let hogwartsQA = [
  {
    question: "In what house is Pansy Parkinson?",
    answers: {
      a: "Gryffindor",
      b: "Ravenclaw",
      c: "Slytherin",
      d: "Hufflepuff",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Slytherin",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Hagrid's boarhound dog?",
    answers: { a: "Fang", b: "Bing", c: "Fluffy", d: "Snoopy" },
    correctAnswer: "1",
  },
  {
    question: "When is Harrys Birthday?",
    answers: {
      a: "August 15",
      b: "January 30",
      c: "July 31",
      d: "Juni 25",
    },
    correctAnswer: "July 31",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Harrysmiddle name?",
    answers: { a: "James", b: "Sirius", c: "Albus", d: "Godric" },
    correctAnswer: "James",
  },
  {
    question: "Who sent Harry his Firebolt?",
    answers: {
      a: "Albus Dumbledor",
      b: "Sirius Black ",
      c: "Minerva McGonagall",
      d: "Remus Lupin",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Sirius Black ",
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of pet does Harry own?",
    answers: { a: "Owl", b: "Cat", c: "Frog", d: "Rat" },
    correctAnswer: "Owl",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Harrys aunt?",
    answers: { a: "Petunia", b: "Beatrice", c: "Minerva", d: "Lavender" },
    correctAnswer: "Petunia",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What painting guards the entrance to the Gryffindor common room?",
    answers: {
      a: "The strong hunter",
      b: "The Fat Lady",
      c: "The smart girl",
      d: "The dangerous ghost",
    },
    correctAnswer: "The Fat Lady",
  },
  {
    question: "Where in Kings Cross Station does the Hogwarts Express stop?",
    answers: {
      a: "Platform 4 and ¾",
      b: "Platform 8 and ¾",
      c: "Platform 9 and ¾",
      d: "Platform 7 and ¾",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Platform 9 and ¾",
  },
  {
    question: "What type of creature is Fluffy?",
    answers: {
      a: "A three-eyed dog",
      b: "A three-headed dog",
      c: "A three-armed dog",
      d: "A three-leged dog",
    },
    correctAnswer: "A three-headed dog",
  },
  {
    question: "Which spell can levitate an object?",
    answers: {
      a: "Expecto Patronum",
      b: "Wingardium Leviosa",
      c: "Expelliarmus",
      d: "Alohomora",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Wingardium Leviosa",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who anonymously sends Harry his father's Invisibility Cloak on Christmas?",
    answers: {
      a: "Minerva McGonagall",
      b: "Sirius Black",
      c: "Remus Lupin",
      d: "Albus Dumbledore",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Albus Dumbledore",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the Weasley family home?",
    answers: {
      a: "The Shanty",
      b: "The Hut",
      c: "The Cabin",
      d: "The Burrow",
    },
    correctAnswer: "The Burrow",
  },
];
